* Use Cases

* * *

* Use Cases

* * *

 ADscore

ADscore

Email

Password

Sign In

 Remember Me

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated date: April 12th, 2019

This Policy
-----------

This privacy policy explains how **Adscore Technologies DMCC** and its subsidiaries (**“Adscore”**, **“we“**, **“us”** or **“our“**) collect, use and disclose information (**“personal data”** as defined further below) which we collect through our solution (**“Platform“**).

Adscore provides its customers (online advertisers, online publishers and ad networks) (**“Web Traffic Processor”**) with transparency and accountability by identifying and detecting fraudulent or invalid traffic purchased through digital advertising (**“Services”**).

Adscore provides two types of services to its users:

* Traffic Verification Services, available through a variety of methods, in order to enable the users to verify the type and origin of their traffic (**“Adscore Verification Services”**) and
* Traffic Reporting Services, available through a web-based dashboard, in order to enable the users to report on the type of traffic they receiveid (**“Adscore Reporting Services”**)

This platform privacy policy explains who we are, what personal data we collect, why and how we process personal data, whom we share your personal data with, and, if you are the subject of any of the personal data concerned, what rights you have and how to get in touch with us if you need to.

**Please read the following carefully to understand our use of your personal data through our Services (as defined below).**

### Changes To This Policy

Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time.

Who We Are
----------

Adscore is a software company that works with Web Traffic Processors to help them identify fraudulent traffic they may be purchasing as part of the advertising ecosystem. To do this, Adscore collects and processes personal data on online users, through the Platform. Reducing fraudulent and invalid activity increases faith in digital advertising.

Adscore’s disclosure of personal data is very limited, as we only temporarily process the data in order to compute statistics before discarding it. The duration during which we hold the data is 1 second, and further details can be obtained by consulting the section “Who we share personal data with”

### What Do You Mean By Personal Data?

“Personal Data” is defined as any data relating to a living individual who can be identified directly from that data or indirectly in conjunction with other information. It can take the form of a name or address and, now, under new data protection laws in Europe, this can extend to uniquely generated IDs, IP addresses and other “unique identifiers”.

We cannot identify an online user by name, or find out where they live, but instead it gives us a picture of how a user interacts with an advertising campaign which we may be monitoring in order to detect fraudulent or invalid traffic.

Personal Data We Collect And How & Why We Collect It
----------------------------------------------------

### Personal Data We Collect

As part of our Services, we collect and process the following information:

* IP address;
* country location;
* cookie IDs.;
* HTTP header data (including Digital Property address, operating system, plug in,)..
* Internet connection type and speed
* browser type, version and capabilities

The combination of this information, with a unique identifier is personal data. We do not collect and process any Special Personal Data.

### How Do We Collect Personal Data?

For Traffic Verification Services, Adscore collects information about your IP address, internet connection type and speed, and browser capabilities, processes them for the duration of 1 second, and then automatically deletes them. Based on the collected data, Adscore aggregates statistics that will be presented to the user in a web dashboard. No cookies, flash codes and other similar technologies are used, and no tracking of the visitor is performed.

For Traffic Reporting Services, Adscore collects usual information about its users in order to continuously improve its service, based on its legitimate business interests. To this extent, Adscore may use pixels, javascript, flash codes, cookies and other similar technologies that will collect information about content interaction. Cookies are small text files placed in visitors’ computer browsers. In the case of Traffic Reporting Services, Adscore will store personal data as such:

* 1 year for anonymous (not logged in) users that have agreed to our tracking policy once they visited our website
* the lifetime of the user account for users that have created an account with us

### Cookies

Adscore collects information and uses tracking mechanisms such as cookies in order to provide the Traffic Reporting Services. No cookies are used for our Traffic Verification Services. We use these cookies and other technologies in our legitimate interests (where we have considered that these are not overridden by your rights).

We use the following types of cookies:

* **Analytical/performance cookies**. They allow us to see how users move around the web pages associated with our Traffic Reporting Service when they are using it.
* **Functionality cookies**. These are used to recognise you when you return to the web pages associated with our Traffic Reporting Service.

End users can configure their browser preferences not to accept these cookies however this may result in reduced functionality for our Traffic Reporting Services. No difference in functionality should be expected for our Traffic Verification Service.

### Why We Collect Personal Data And Our Lawful Basis For Processing

Adscore collects information, including personal data, in order to identify and prevent fraud online (including in respect of online advertising and ecommerce). We also use such information for our internal operations (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing and statistical purposes). We do not use any personal data other than as necessary to execute our Services.

Adscore does not collect, retain, or share any personally identifiable information ("PII") (including unique user identifiers and IP addresses) gathered on sites or apps not owned by Adscore ("Third Party Provided PII"), except for the purpose of providing our fraud detection and prevention related services and never to create user profiles. We only share Third Party Provided PII with customers receiving our fraud detection and prevention services, or as otherwise directed by the applicable customer and services providers if necessary to provide the fraud detection and prevention services to our customers. We never share Third Party Provided PII collected on one customer’s site with other customers. Retention of Third Party Provided PII is determined by the applicable customers.

EU Privacy law requires us to have a “lawful basis” for collecting and using processing data. We collect this information for our legitimate interests. These are two fold (a) our legitimate interest, and our client’s legitimate interest, in preventing fraud; and (b) our legitimate interest in managing client relationships and the ongoing improvement of our Services.

Who We Share Personal Data With
-------------------------------

Adscore may disclose personal data to third parties in the following ways:

* We may disclose personal data to our affiliates subject to these obligations.
* **Service Providers**. We may disclose personal data to our third-party service provider Google.
* **Clients**. We provide our clients (who nevertheless already have access to all of their data that we monitor) with access to aggregate information.
* **Compliance and Safety**. We may disclose personal data as necessary or appropriate under applicable laws to: comply with legal process or requirements, including applicable notification obligations; respond to requests from public and government authorities (including public and government authorities outside your country of residence); enforce our terms and conditions; and protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates and our rights, privacy, safety, or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others.
* **Merger, Sale, Etc**. We may disclose personal data in the event of a proposed or actual reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of Adscore’s business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

How We Secure Your Personal Data
--------------------------------

We seek to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your personal data collected, used and processed by us as part of the Services, using reasonably high standard security measures (such as encryption and other applicable measures based on the type of personal data and applicable processing activity).

How Long Do We Process Personal Data For?
-----------------------------------------

For Traffic Verification Services, we process personal data for 1 second, after which it is automatically deleted.

For Traffic Reporting Services, we process personal data for 12 months (not logged in users), or for the lifetime of the account for users who have created an account with us. After this period, we will delete the personal data except to the extent that it is necessary for us to continue to process it for the purpose of compliance with legal obligations to which we are subject or for another legitimate and lawful purpose.

We may aggregate and keep non-personal data for as long as is necessary for us to provide and improve our services but not in a way that would identify you personally.

Where Do We Process Personal Data?
----------------------------------

The data that we process in relation to users may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA“) that may not be subject to equivalent data protection law. It may also be processed by staff situated outside the EEA who works for us or for one of our suppliers.

* In order to store it.
* Where we are legally required to do so.
* In order to facilitate the operation of our group of businesses, where it is in our legitimate interests and we have concluded these are not overridden by your rights.

Where personal data is transferred by us or our affiliates in relation to providing our services we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that it is subject to appropriate safeguards, such as relying on a recognised legal adequacy mechanism which may include by entering into EC approved standard contractual clauses relevant to transfers of personal information (see [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/dataprotection/internationaltransfers/transfer/index\_en.html](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/dataprotection/internationaltransfers/transfer/index_en.html)) and that it is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

We may transfer your personal information to the following:

* Any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, including United Arab Emirates and the US.
* When transferring EEA data to United Arab Emirates, we rely on the European Commission’s decision that United Arab Emirates offers adequate data protection for transfers from the EEA.
* When transferring EEA data to the US, we rely on the EU-US Privacy Shield.

What Are Your Rights?
---------------------

You have the following rights in relation to personal data relating to you that we process:

* You may request access to the personal data concerned (please see the section on obtaining access to your personal data, below).
* You may request that any incorrect personal data about you that we are processing be rectified.
* In certain circumstances (normally where the personal data has been provided by you and it is no longer necessary for us to continue to process it), you may be entitled to request that we erase the personal data concerned subject to some specific legal reasons we may have to retain certain data relating to you.
* You may, in certain circumstances, object to the further processing of your personal data.
* You may request that your provided personal data be moved to a third party.

If you have a complaint about any processing of your personal data being conducted by us, you can contact us.

### How To Exercise Your Rights

You can exercise your rights as follows:

* By contacting support using this public page's Contact buttons.
* By contacting supoort using the Dashboard's Support button.

Please note that we ask you for further information in order to confirm your identity before we provide any information requested or enact your request. If your request or concern is not satisfactorily resolved by us, you may approach your local data protection authority (to your habitual residence, your place of work, or an alleged infringement of the GDPR) (see [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index\_en.html](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.html)).

The Information Commissioner is the supervisory authority in the UK and can provide further information about your rights and our obligations in relation to your personal data, as well as deal with any complaints that you have about our processing of your personal data.

### Our Details — Contacting Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, the information practices of the Platform, or your dealings with Adscore, you can contact us at any time:

#### Adscore Technologies DMCC

**Office 1906, Jumeirah Business Center 5**  
**Cluster W, Jumeirah Lake Towers**  
**Dubai, UAE**  
**P.O. BOX 282060**

* Use Cases

* * *

* Forgot Password

© Copyright Adscore Technologies DMCC 2024. All content and images are copyrighted.

Get in touch

Get to see how Adscore works
